<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Metaverse,Next meta space!</title>
    <link>https://nextmetaspace.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Metaverse,Next meta space!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nextmetaspace.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://nextmetaspace.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nextmetaspace.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there My name is Next.Meta.Space!
So, there you have it&amp;hellip; enjoy!</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hi-there&#34;&gt;Hi there&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Next.Meta.Space!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, there you have it&amp;hellip; enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Friend,What&#39;s Next Meta Space? Metaverse!</title>
      <link>https://nextmetaspace.github.io/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nextmetaspace.github.io/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>Metaverse - Next Meta Space! Information The metaverse (a portmanteau of &amp;ldquo;meta-&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;universe&amp;rdquo;) is a hypothesized iteration of the internet, supporting persistent online 3-D virtual environments through conventional personal computing, as well as virtual and augmented reality headsets. Metaverses, in some limited form, are already present on platforms like VRChat or video games like Second Life.
Current metaverse ambitions are centered on addressing technological limitations with modern virtual and augmented reality devices, as well as expanding the use of metaverse spaces to business, education, and retail applications.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;metaverse---next-meta-space&#34;&gt;Metaverse - Next Meta Space!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;information&#34;&gt;Information&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The metaverse (a portmanteau of &amp;ldquo;meta-&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;universe&amp;rdquo;) is a hypothesized iteration of the internet, supporting persistent online 3-D virtual environments through conventional personal computing, as well as virtual and augmented reality headsets. Metaverses, in some limited form, are already present on platforms like VRChat or video games like Second Life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current metaverse ambitions are centered on addressing technological limitations with modern virtual and augmented reality devices, as well as expanding the use of metaverse spaces to business, education, and retail applications. Numerous entertainment and social media companies have invested in metaverse-related research and development&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;elements&#34;&gt;Elements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some iterations of the metaverse involve integration between virtual and physical spaces and invented economies. Additional qualities include digital persistence and synchronicity in order to better establish a sense of presence in a realistic environment. The metaverse ecosystem encompasses user-centric elements including avatar identity, content creation, virtual economy, social acceptability, presence, security and privacy, and trust and accountability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;timeline-of-notable-developments&#34;&gt;Timeline of notable developments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1978 – MUDs and MOOs are multi-user virtual environments often based on a map of connected locations and described in text to the users who navigated through the environment and the puzzles with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1993 – The Metaverse was a MOO (a text-based, low-bandwidth virtual reality system) operated by Steve Jackson Games as part of their BBS, Illuminati Online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1995 – Active Worlds, based entirely on Snow Crash, distributed virtual-reality worlds implementing at least the concept of the metaverse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2003 – Second Life was launched by Linden Lab. The stated goal of the project was to create a user-defined world like the metaverse in which people can interact, play, do business, and otherwise communicate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2004 – X3D was approved by ISO as the successor to the Virtual Reality Modeling Language (VRML) as the open standard for interactive real-time 3D (web3D). Today X3D is the standard defining the 3D web and mixed reality open metaverse by combining virtual, mirror, and augmented realities with the web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2006 – Roblox was published.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2018 – NeosVR Metaverse was launched by Solirax.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2019 – Facebook Horizon was announced as a social VR world by Facebook.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2020 – Decentraland launched as a decentralized virtual platform owned and operated by its users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2021 – Epic Games directs fundraising to build out Fortnite into a metaverse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2021 – Microsoft Mesh, a mixed reality software enabling virtual presence through Microsoft devices such as the HoloLens 2, was announced.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2021 – South Korea announces the creation of a national metaverse alliance with the goal to build a unified national VR and AR platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2021 – The parent company of the social network Facebook is renamed from &amp;ldquo;Facebook, Inc.&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Meta Platforms&amp;rdquo;. Its chairman Mark Zuckerberg declared a company commitment to developing a metaverse ecosystem. Various augmented and virtual reality concepts are presented, though much of the underlying technology remains in or has yet to enter development.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
